YOUSSOU NDIAYE

CONTACT

Q Lor

London CR4 3PJ

(() (

07395429645

Y

youssou467@icloud.com

SKILLS

- Credit and cash transactions
- Store merchandise handling
- Customer assistance
- · Cash counting
- Bilingual (fluent in Italian as well as English)
- Outgoing and enthusiastic
- Excellent verbal communication
- excellent time management

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- I model for two agencies: Xdirectn in London and INDEPENDENT in Milan
- been a member of an organisation called Blackmindsmatter for the WCEN

LANGUAGES				
Italian: First Language				
Italian:				C2
Proficient				
wolof:				C2
Proficient				
English:				C2
Proficient				

Hardworking and reliable worker with strong background in operating cash registers, stocking merchandise and keeping areas clean and neat. Highly organised, proactive and punctual with teamoriented mentality. Motivated with two-year track record of success in providing exceptional service and sales support in busy and fast-paced environments. Offering exceptional communicational and managerial abilities. Strong team player committed to assisting coworkers and management with all activities necessary for store success.

EXPERIENCE

June 2022 - September 2022

Runner Boulevard, London

- Welcomed guests with polite and friendly manner, fostering positive experience.
- Supported bar team, finishing drinks with garnishes and running orders to accommodate busy shifts. Identified and resolved safety hazards to safeguard teams and products.
- Cleaned and organized workstations and common areas to increase efficiency.
- Logged daily duties in company logs, detailing hours works and materials used.
- Communicated tactfully to address and resolve customer dissatisfaction, relaying critical issues to management.
- Adhered to heath and safety requirements related to safe food-handling and kitchen sanitisation.

Costumer Assistant Oxfam Charity Shop, London

- Helped customers on the shop floor and directed them to their desired clothing departments.
- organised clothes by department and colours.
- price-tagged clothing items
- un-packed various clothing donations and had to sort out which could be sold and which had to be disposed of.
- supervised customer behaviour in the shop floor

January 2020 - August 2021

Front Counter Cashier Burger King, London

- Smoothly processed incoming orders, handling over 100 transactions per day with exceptional accuracy.
- Worked overtime shifts to maintain optimal workflow during busy periods or times of unexpected high volume.
- Observed company return policy when processing refunds.
- Maintained high productivity by efficiently processing cash, credit and debit payments for customers.

January 2019 - August 2019

kitchen staff Mcdonalds, London

- Kept kitchen operations efficient and organised by storing kitchen supplies in designated areas.
- Prepared ingredients for dishes as requested by chefs, carrying out tasks such as peeling, chopping and washing.

- Kept operations running smoothly and efficiently by keeping workspaces organised, clean and ready for service.
- Assisted in kitchen closing duties, carrying out tasks such as sanitation, calculating waste and organising stock for next day opening.

EDUCATION

GCSEs

Springwest Academy, Feltham, HNS

- English literature- grade 6
- English language-grade 5
- spanish-grade 8
- combined science-grade 5:5
- Mathematics- grade 4
- Drama- grade 4
- English as a second language- grade 7
- Coursework in Travel and Tourism- Merit at level 2

Saint Francis Xavier sixth form college, City of London, LND

- Religious studies- grade A*
- Italian- grade A*
- psychology- grade A
- Sociology-grade B